ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILGWU #2 - 6/5/86, 1986 (Box 288, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #1 - 6/6/86, 1986 (Box 289, Folder 1)
- ILGWU #2 - 6/6/86, 1986 (Box 290, Folder 1)
- Bayard Rustin. The Singer (Box 293, Folder 1)
- Bayard Rustin. The Singer (Box 294, Folder 1)
- Bayard Rustin. The Singer (Box 295, Folder 1)
- Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs (Box 299, Folder 1)
- Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs (Box 300, Folder 1)
- Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs (Box 301, Folder 1)